伟大富强的人类第四帝国
The Fourth Great and Bountiful Human Empire.
全帝国大事小情都从这里播发出去
Every single fact in the Empire beams out of this place.
我说这才叫权力
That's what I call power.
600个频道 全都播发自五号卫星
600 channels coming out of Satellite Five,
把信号输送到每个角落
broadcasting everywhere.
这个技术有问题
This technology's wrong.
有麻烦吗
Trouble?
对
Oh, yeah.
这里并不是伟大富强的人类第四帝国
This is not the Fourth Great and Bountiful Human Empire.
是我的客户好心让人类在这儿居住的
Humans are allowed to live here by kind permission of my client.
五号卫星受谁控制
Who controls Satellite Five?
来自神圣哈杰西马科斯多佛的伟大加戈菲斯
The Mighty Jagrafess of the Holy Hadrojassic Maxarodenfoe.
你是说那玩意掌控着五号卫星吗
You mean that thing's in charge of Satellite Five?
只要去了500层 就回不来了
Once you go to Floor 500, you never come back.
你们得留在这解释 没人会相信我的
You'll have to stay and explain it, no-one's gonna believe me.
他们相信很多事
Oh, they might start believing a lot of things now.
人类应该加速发展 回归正常
The human race should accelerate. All back to normal.
一个世纪以后
怎么了 发生了什么
What is it? What's happening?
天呐
Oh, my God!
简直不敢相信 他们为什么把你丢在那里
I don't believe it, why did they put you in there?
他们都没通知你要来
They never said you were coming!
怎么回事 我…
What happened? I was...
小心点
Careful now, oh...
留神
Oh, mind yourself!
都怪物质粒子传输器
Oh, that's the transmat,
让人头晕脑胀 我当初难受了好几天
it scrambles your head. I was sick for days.
你没事吧
You all right?
你叫什么名字 亲爱的
So... what's your name, then, sweetheart?
博士 我想应该是 我…
The Doctor, I think, I was...
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what happened!
你被选中了
You got chosen.
被选中干什么
Chosen for what?
你现在是房客 已经在房子里了 棒不棒
You're a housemate! You're in the house! Isn't that brilliant?
这不公平 还有五分钟就要开始淘汰了
That's not fair, we've got eviction in five minutes!
我已经在这里待了九周了 遵守了所有规则
I've been here for all nine weeks, I've followed the rules,
我没有得到任何警告 现在他来了
I haven't had a single warning, and he comes swanning in!
如果他们不停地更改规则 我要抗议了
If they keep changing the rules, I'm gonna protest, I am.
你看着 我要写大字报
You watch me. I'm gonna paint the walls.
有请博士到日记屋来
'Would the Doctor please come to the Diary Room?'
本节目现在由第44000频道直播
You are live on Channel 44, 000.
请不要说脏话
Please do not swear.
你这是在逗我
You have GOT to be kidding.
神秘博士第一季第十二集
恶狼
怎么回事
What happened?
没事的
It's all right.
都怪物质粒子传输器
It's the transmat.
搅乱你的脑子 会有点失忆
It does your head in, you get a bit of amnesia.
你叫什么
What's your name?
洛斯 博士在哪儿
Rose. But... where's the Doctor?
千万记住 按安卓机器人说的做
Just remember, do what the android says.
别刺激它
Don't provoke it.
它的话就是王法
The android's word is law.
你说的安卓机器人是什么 机器人吗
What do you mean, android? Like a robot?
各就各位 所有人 谢谢
Positions, everyone, thank you!
来吧 快点
Come on, hurry up!
稳住
Oh, steady!
我之前在旅行
I was travelling,
和博士还有名为杰克的上校一起
with the Doctor and a man called Captain Jack.
博士不会抛下我
The Doctor wouldn't just leave me.
别聊了
That's enough chat!
就位 最后一次 好运
Positions! Final call. Good luck.
我不应该在这里
But I'm not supposed to be here.
台上写着你的名字
It says Rose on the podium.
快点
Come on.
等一下
Hold on...
我一定是疯了
I must be going mad.
不可能 这简直就是…
It can't be, this looks like...
安卓机器人启动
Android activated!
天呐 安卓机器人
Oh, my God, the android...
机器版安·罗宾逊
The An...Droid.
欢迎来到《智者为王》
Welcome...To the Weakest Link!
又来了 每次都得花大力气改造
Here we go again. We've got our work cut out for us.
我不确定 他还蛮帅的 下巴不错
I don't know, he's sort of handsome. Good lantern jaw.
他这下巴已经过时了
Lantern jaws are so last year.
抱歉 很高兴认识你们 女士们
Sorry... Nice to meet you, ladies,
但是我这是在哪
but where exactly am I?
我们要给你一个全新的形象
We're giving you a brand new image.
等一下 我之前是跟博士在一起
Hold on, I was with the Doctor...
怎么了 我穿的有什么不对吗
Why, is there something wrong with what I'm wearing?
你的衣服都非常有20世纪风
It's all very 20th century,
你哪里找来的牛仔布
where did you get that denim?
卡迪夫的一家小店 叫天下第一店
A little place in Cardiff, it was called...The Top Shop.
经典设计
Ah, design classic!
我们去找些新颜色给你
We're gonna have to find you some new colours,
除掉你现在身上那种俄克拉荷马农夫的感觉
maybe get rid of that Oklahoma farm boy thing you've got going.
站着别动 让褪衣器发挥作用
Just stand still and let the defabricator work its magic.
什么是褪衣器
What's a defabricator?
好吧 褪衣器 果然名不虚传
OK, defabricator. Does exactly what it says on the tin.
我现在是不是全裸出现在数百万观众面前
Am I naked in front of millions of viewers?
正是
Absolutely!
女士们 你们的收视率暴涨啦
Ladies...Your viewing figures just went up.
打不开
I can't open it.
所有门都锁死了
It's got a deadlock seal,
自从第504集 他们全体出走之后
ever since Big Brother 504 when they all walked out.
那次你总该记得吧
You must remember that.
这个呢
What about this?
那是复合玻璃纤维
Oh, that's exoglass,
要原子弹才能穿透
you'd need a nuclear bomb to get through.
你这话只会让我更想尝试
Don't tempt me.
我知道我们不能谈外面的情况
I know you're not supposed to talk about the outside world,
但是你肯定有一直在看这个节目
but you must've been watching.
人们喜欢我吗
Do people like me?
琳达 王字边的琳 不是林达
Lynda, Lynda with a Y, not Linda with an I,
她因为损毁摄像机被强制淘汰了
she got forcibly evicted cos she damaged a camera.
我受欢迎吗
Am I popular?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
你是说我无关紧要吗
Oh, but does that mean I'm nothing?
有些人留到现在就因为他们无足轻重
Some people get this far just cos they're insignificant.
没有人留意我吗
Doesn't anybody notice me?
不是的 你很好 你很可爱
No, you're nice, you're sweet.
大家都觉得你可爱
Everybody thinks you're sweet.
是这样吗 我是那样的吗
Oh, is that right? Is that what I am?
没人这么跟我说过
No-one's ever told me that before.
我可爱 真的吗
Am I sweet? Really?
是的 可爱极了
Yeah, dead sweet.
谢谢
Thank you.
那堵墙 那外面难道不应该有个花园吗
It's a wall. Isn't there supposed to be a garden out there?
别傻了 没人有花园 现在谁还有花园
Don't be daft, no-one's got a garden any more! Who's got a garden?
别跟我说你有花园
Don't tell me you've got a garden!
没有 我只有塔迪斯
No, I've just got the Tardis.
我想起来了
I remember.
你想起来了 那么他们是从哪儿找到你们的
That's the amnesia! So what happened, where did they get you?
我们刚离开拉克西科里科弗拉帕多里斯星
We'd just left Raxacoricofallapatorius
然后去了京都
and then we went to Kyoto,
没错 1336年的日本
that's right, Japan in 1336,
我们刚逃出来
and we only just escaped.
我们三个笑成一团
We were together and we were laughing and then...
突然有一道光
there was this light,
一道白光穿透墙壁 然后
this white light coming through the walls, and then...
我就在这里醒来了
I woke up here.
那就是物质粒子传输射线
Yeah, that's the transmat beam,
他们用那个来挑选房客
that's how they pick the housemates.
王字边的琳达
Oh, Lynda with a Y...
可爱的琳达
Sweet little Lynda.
比那糟糕的多
It's worse than that.
我可不是什么随便的过客
I'm not just some passing traveller.
没有传输射线能穿透我的船
No stupid little transmat gets inside my ship.
那道光线的功率得有传输射线的1500万倍
That beam was 15 million times more powerful,
也就是说 这不仅仅是个游戏
which means... this isn't just a game.
这里还有别的事情在发生
There's something else going on.
来自《老大哥》的最新消息
Well, here's the latest update from the Big Brother house.
我要出去
I'm getting out,
我会找到我的朋友
I'm gonna find my friends...
然后 我会找到你
and then I'm gonna find you.
有事跟你说
Need a word.
等一下
Hold on.
让我先把这个弄完 19 18
Let me finish this. 19, 18...
17 16 15
17, 16, 15...
谢谢各位 马上开始直播
Thank you, people, transmitting in...
12 11 10
12, 11, 10...
我要去找博士 -闭上嘴 好好玩游戏
But I need to find the Doctor. - Just shut up and play the game!
那好吧 管他呢
All right, then... What the hell?
我会赢的
I'm gonna play to win!
开始
And... cue.
《智者为王》现在开始
Let's play the Weakest Link!
开始计时 阿格拉斯 什么食物
Start the clock. Agorax, the name of
名称是单词"胡须"的变形
which basic foodstuff is an anagram of the word "Beard"?
面包
Bread.
正确
Correct.
斐奇 潘彻菲克历中 胡布月后是什么月
Fitch, in the Pantraffic Calendar, which month comes after Hoob?
是克拉维多月吗
Is it...Clavadoe?
错 是潘多夫月
No, Pandoff.
洛斯 数学题 258减158是多少
Rose, in maths, what is 258 minus 158?
一百
100.
正确 罗德里克
Correct. Rodrick.
存档
Bank!
哪个字母出现在了单词"Dangle"中
Which letter of the alphabet appears in the word "Dangle"
但没有出现在单词"Gland"中
but not in the word "Gland"?
字母 E
E.
正确
Correct.
珂林 社保系统中
Colleen, in social security,
火星无人机的报酬被称作什么
what D is the name of payment given to martian drones
默认金
Default.
正确
Correct.
布罗夫 伟大的钴金字塔
Broff, the Great Cobalt Pyramid
建立在哪个著名的古地球机构的遗迹之上
is built on the remains of which famous old Earth institute?
火鸡木
Touchdown.
错 是火炬木
No, Torchwood.
阿格拉斯 语言知识 全部五种什么字母
Agorax, in language, all five examples of which type of letter
都出现在了单词"facetious"中
appear in the word facetious?
元音字母
Vowels.
正确
Correct.
斐奇 生物知识
Fitch, in biology,
那种细胞含铁元素 红细胞还是白细胞
which blood cells contain iron - red or white?
白细胞
White.
错 是红细胞
No, red.
洛斯 全息剧集《木星上行》中
Rose, in the holovid series Jupiter Rising,
格斯尼克与谁结了婚
the Grexnik is married to whom?
我怎么会知道
How should I know?
她为什么要笑
Why is she laughing?
罗德里克 数学题
Rodrick, in maths...
天呐 我觉得她知道了
Oh, my God, I think she knows.
我这边有一个凭空出现的房客
And I've got a housemate who appeared out of nowhere.
跟你说了 就好像这些游戏在自行运转一样
I told you. It's like the game's running itself.
这是海盗型 一点海盗风
It's the buccaneer look - a little a dash of pirate
加上一点施瓦辛格州长的风格
and just a tweak of President Schwarzenegger.
我不是很喜欢这个背心
I'm not sure about the vest,
加点颜色提亮一下怎么样
what about a bit of colour to lift it?
绝对不行 绝对不要用彩色和黑色搭配
Absolutely not, never wear black with colour.
显得彩色俗气而黑色古板
It makes the colour looks cheap and the black boring.
来看下外套
Now, let's talk jackets.
我挺喜欢第一件
I kinda like the first one.
不行 太像地狱天使了
No, that's a bit too much Hell's Angel,
我觉得短的这件好些
I think I like the shorter one.
长度到腰 好看显瘦 突显臀部
Look, waist-length, nice and slimming, shows off the bum.
我喜欢
Works for me.
服装挑好了之后 我们就可以来看脸部了
Once we've got an outfit, we can look at the face.
考虑过整容吗
Ever thought about cosmetic surgery?
考虑过 把眼周提升一点
I've considered it. A little lift around the eyes,
再让下巴线条紧致一些
tighten up the jaw line.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
再大胆一些
Oh, let's have a bit more ambition!
做一些前卫的风格
Let's do something...Cutting edge.
那么 洛斯 你是做什么的
So, Rose, what do you actually do?
四处旅行
I just travel about a bit,
算是旅行家吧 我想
a bit of a...Tourist, I suppose.
也就是无业游民 -不是
Another way of saying unemployed? - No.
你有工作吗
Have you got a job?
是没有 但是
Well, not really, no, but...
那你就是无业游民啊 但是
Then you ARE unemployed, and yet
你还是有钱买漂发剂 为什么选斐奇
you've still got enough money to buy peroxide. Why Fitch?
我觉得她答错了几个问题
I think she got a few of the questions wrong,
就这样 -所以说那些题你都会吗
that's all. - And you'd know all about that.
但是我又不能选自己 那就只能是斐奇了
Well, yeah, but I can't vote for myself, so it had to be Fitch.
抱歉 游戏就是这样 这是规则
I'm sorry, that's the game, that's how it works.
我总得选个人淘汰
I had to vote someone.
让我再试一次 都怪这些灯光
Let me try again, it was the lights and everything,
害我脑子不转
I couldn't think.
事实上 布罗夫答错了三道题
In fact, with three answers wrong, Broff
他才是这轮最弱一环 但以投票为准
was the weakest link in that round, but it's votes that count.
对不起
I'm sorry, please...
天呐 救救我
Oh, God, help me!
斐奇 你是最弱一环 再见
Fitch, you are the weakest link. Goodbye.
现在插播广告 三分钟后继续
And we've gone to the adverts, back in three minutes!
怎么回事 刚发生了什么
What was that? What just happened?
她是最弱一环 所以被解体了
She was the weakest link, she gets disintegrated.
分解为原子
Blasted into atoms.
我还投了她一票
But I voted for her!
天呐 这简直变态
Oh, my God, this is sick!
你们所有人 都是变态
All of you, you're just sick!
我不玩了
I'm not playing!
我玩不下去了
I... I can't do it!
拜托 谁来放我出去
Oh, please, somebody let me out!
你是最弱一环
You are the weakest link.
再见
Goodbye.
别想着逃跑
Don't try to escape.
不是玩就是死
It's play... or die.
博士 他们说所有房客都要坐到沙发上
Doctor, they said all housemates must gather on the sofa,
你也得坐下来
you've got to.
我急着要出去 多谢
I'm busy getting out, thanks.
但如果你不遵守规则 所有房客都要受罚
But if you don't obey, then all the housemates get punished.
那你们可以投票淘汰我
Well, maybe I'll be voted out, then.
你有多蠢 你刚加入 不能淘汰你
How stupid are you? You've only just joined, you're not eligible.
别耍花招 不然我们都会挨重罚的
Don't try anything clever or we all get it in the neck.
老大哥之家的房客们 我是戴维娜机器人
Big Brother house, this is Davina-droid.
克洛斯比 琳达 斯特罗德
Crosbie, Lynda and Strood,
你们被提名为淘汰候选人
you have all been nominated for eviction.
第八个被老大哥淘汰的是
And the eighth person to be evicted from the Big Brother house is...
克洛斯比
Crosbie!
我好抱歉 我好抱歉
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
本该是我 这不公平 -克洛斯比
It should've been me, that's not fair. - Oh, Crosbie...
克洛斯比 你有十秒钟道别
Crosbie, you have ten seconds to
然后我们就来找你了
make your farewells and then we're gonna get you.
我不会忘记你
I won't forget you!
抱歉偷了你的肥皂
I'm sorry I stole your soap.
没关系 真的
I don't mind, honestly!
谢谢你做的饭 好吃极了 祝你好运
Thanks for the food, you were a smashing cook, bless you.
克洛斯比 请离开老大哥之家
Crosbie, please leave the Big Brother house.
再见了 再见 琳达
Bye, then. Bye, Lynda.
简直不敢相信 可怜的克洛斯比
I don't believe it, poor Crosbie.
不过是个真人秀 她出去以后就能大捞一笔
It's only a game show! She'll make a fortune on the outside.
写书 出唱片
Sell her story, release a record,
录制健身视频什么的 她开心都来不及
fitness video, all of that, she'll be laughing.
出去以后 你是什么意思
What do you mean, on the outside?
开始了
Here we go.
他们在等什么
Well, what are they waiting for?
为什么不干脆点让她走
Why don't they just let her go?
别说了 一点也不好笑
Stop it, it's not funny!
五 四 三
Eviction in five, four,
二 一 淘汰
three, two, one!
那是怎么回事
What was that?
解体光线
Disintegrator beam.
她被淘汰了
She's been evicted.
被杀死了
From life.
没有人为传输器编程
No-one programmed the transmat,
没人挑选新的选手
no-one selected the new contestants.
就像那些故事里说的一样
It is exactly like those stories.
别再说了
Oh, don't start that again.
我觉得你需要休息一下
I think you need to take a session off.
你跟我一起的话我很乐意
I would, if you'd take it with me.
这个也别再提了
And don't start that again either.
但是好几十年前就有谣言
Though the rumours go back decades,
声称有东西藏在这上面
saying that something's been hidden up here
藏在传输信号之下
underneath the transmissions.
但是主控会知道的
But the controller would know.
她监视着一切
She watches everything.
也许她看不见
Maybe she just can't see it.
你得考虑人为错误
You've got to allow for human error.
问题就在这里
Well, that's your problem, then.
我觉得很多年前她就已经不是人了
I don't think she's been human for years.
18 19 20
18, 19, 20,
21 22 23 传输
21, 22, 23, transmit.
你们疯了吗
Are you insane?
你们就那么走进去被解体
You just step right into the disintegrator?
上电视就那么重要吗
Is it that important, getting your face on the telly?
值得你们去死
Is it worth dying for? !
你说得我们好像可以选择似的
You're talking like we haven't got a choice!
我以为你们要申请参加
But I thought you had to apply.
别傻了 那是几个世纪之前的事了
Don't be so stupid, that's how they played it centuries back.
无论你喜不喜欢 你都会被选中
You get chosen whether you like it or not.
地球上的每个人都是候选人
Everyone on Earth is a potential contestant,
传输射线随机挑选
the transmat beam picks you out at random.
永不停歇 同时有60个老大哥之家在运作
It's non-stop, there are 60 Big Brother Houses running at once.
几个 60
How many, 60?!
他们不得不缩减数量 没有以前那么多了
They've had to cut back, it's not what it was.
这简直就是停尸房
It's a charnel house!
那优胜者呢 他们能得到什么
What about the winners, what do they get?
他们可以活下去
They get to live.
就这样
Is that it? !
还不够吗
Well, isn't that enough?
洛斯还在外面
Rose is out there.
她也被传输过来了 她也是游戏选手
She got caught in the transmat, she's a contestant.
我该走了
Time I got out.
那个选手 没有王字边的林达
That other contestant, Linda with an I,
她因为什么被强制淘汰
she was forcibly evicted for what?
破坏公物
Damage to property.
像这样
What, like this?
我不喜欢这个 这个太…
No, I'm just not getting this, it's just too...
保守 太体面 而且太不耐脏了
safe, too decent. And you'd never keep it clean.
第二阶段准备好开始了
Stage two ready and waiting.
来吧 姑娘们
Bring it on, girls.
到改头换面的时间了
Now it's time for the face-off!
什么意思 我要跟谁打一架吗
Does that mean I get to compete with someone else?
不 就像我说的 改头 换面
No, like I said, face...Off.
给你换个狗头应该看上去不错
I think you'd look good with a dog's head.
或者干脆不要头 那样绝对大胆
Or maybe no head at all, that would be so outrageous.
我们还可以把你的腿缝到胸前
And we could stitch your legs to the middle of your chest.
没什么事不能尝试 值得拼命
Nothing is too extreme, it's to die for!
等一下 女士们
Now hold on, ladies,
我不想冲你们任何一个人开枪
I don't want to have to shoot either one of you.
但是你没有武器 你是全裸好吗
But you're unarmed. You're naked!
但那是豪华压缩激光枪
But that's a Compact Laser Deluxe!
你从哪里拿出来的
Where were you hiding that?
你不想知道的
You really don't want to know.
把那个配饰给我
Give me that accessory!
你是最弱一环 再见
You are the weakest link, goodbye!
休息一下 两分钟后继续
Going to the break, two minutes on the clock.
提醒一下 十分钟后有太阳耀斑活动
Just a reminder, we've got solar flare activity coming up in ten.
珂林很聪明 把钱都存起来了
Colleen was clever, she banked all the money,
你为什么要投票给她
why'd you you vote for her?
因为我想把你留下
Cos I want to keep you in!
你没脑子 甚至不知道沃塞心公主姓什么
You're stupid, you don't even know the Princess Vossaheen's surname.
到决赛的时候 就是我对你
When it comes to the final, I want to be up against you.
结果就是你被解体 我赢得巨额奖金
So that you get disintegrated and I get a load of credits,
感谢恶狼集团
courtesy of the Bad Wolf Corporation.
你什么意思 谁是恶狼
What do you mean? Who's Bad Wolf?
他们掌管一切 他们控制着游戏基站
They're in charge. They run the Game Station.
为什么叫他们恶狼
Why are they called Bad Wolf?
不知道 就是个名字
I dunno, it's just a name.
好像是古老的地球歌谣之类的 有什么关系
It's like an old Earth nursery rhyme, what does it matter?
无论走到哪儿 我总会听到这个词 恶狼
I keep hearing those words everywhere we go, Bad Wolf...
你见到的东西 那些黑暗
The things you've seen... The darkness!
大恶狼
The big bad wolf.
全体注意
Attention, all personnel,
恶狼一号正在降落
Bad Wolf One descending.
什么意思
What does it mean?
恶狼
Bad Wolf.
不同的时间 不同的地方
Different times, different places,
就好像遍布全宇宙
like it's written all over the universe.
你在说什么呢
What are you on about?
如果这场游戏由恶狼控制
If the Bad Wolf are in charge of the quiz, then...
也许我不是偶然来到这里
Maybe I'm not here by mistake.
有人计划了这一切
Someone's been planning this.
博士 你违反了房客守则
The Doctor, you've broken the house rules,
老大哥不得不淘汰你
Big Brother has no choice but to evict you.
你有十秒时间道别
You have ten seconds to make your farewells,
然后我们就要找你了
and then we're gonna get you.
快点 开门
Come on, then, open up!
你疯了 你想死吗
You're mad, it's like you want to die!
我觉得他是被派来搅局的
I reckon he's a plant, he was only brought in to stir things up.
博士 请离开老大哥之家
The Doctor, please leave the Big Brother house.
来啊 动手啊
Come on, then! Disintegrate me!
来啊 你在等什么
Come on, what are you waiting for?
他疯了 脑子坏掉了
He's mad, he's bonkers.
动手啊
Disintegrate me!
我让你看着他 不是杀了他
I told you to keep an eye on him, not kill him.
他破坏了公物 这是自动程序
He damaged the property, it's an automatic process.
五 四
Eviction in five, four...
三 二
three, two...
一
one!
我就知道 看见没
Ha-ha, I knew it! Do you see?
有人故意把我卷进这个游戏
Someone brought me into this game.
如果想让我死 直接把我传输到火山口就行
If they wanted me dead, they could've transmatted me into a volcano.
你干了什么 -什么也没干
What did you do? - Nothing,
就好像有人重写了自动程序
it's like... some sort of override.
也许这边的保安措施没那么严密
Maybe the security isn't as tight this end.
你在看吗 我要出去了
Are you following this? I'm getting out!
跟我走吧
Come with me.
我们不能离开 -留在这儿
We're not allowed! - Stay in there,
你有一半的几率被解体
you've got a 50/50 chance of disintegration.
跟着我 我保证把你活着带出去
Stay with me, I promise I'll get you out alive, come on!
我不能
No, I can't... I can't.
琳达 你很可爱
Lynda, you're sweet.
从我见识到的这个世界来看
From what I've seen of your world,
你觉得有几个人会为可爱投票
do you think anybody votes for sweet?
等一下 我来过这里
Hold on... I've been here before.
这是五号卫星
This is Satellite Five.
没有保安 这倒新鲜
No guards. That makes a change.
像五号卫星这种大企业
You'd think a big business
你以为他们肯定会全副武装
like Satellite Five would be armed to the teeth.
很多年前就没人叫它五号卫星了
No-one's called it Satellite Five in ages.
现在的名字是游戏基站
It's the Game Station now.
100年前这里就不是五号卫星了
It hasn't been Satellite Five in about 100 years.
整整100年 现在是公元200100
100 years exactly. It's the year 200100.
我来过这里 139层
I was here before, Floor 139.
那个时候卫星播送的是新闻
The satellite was broadcasting news channels back then.
跟上面的人闹了点矛盾 没什么大事
I had a bit of trouble upstairs, nothing too serious.
帮了他们一把 就回家喝茶了
Easy, gave 'em a hand, home in time for tea.
100年以前
100 years ago?
你是说你100年前来过这里 -没错
What, you were here 100 years ago? - Yep.
那你保养得不错啊
You're looking good on it.
我经常保湿
I moisturise.
读数都很奇怪 各种能量
Funny sort of readings. All kinds of energy.
这地方满是能量 太奇怪了
The place is humming. It's weird.
这远远超过正常播送的能量
This goes way beyond normal transmissions.
他们需要那么多能量干什么
What would they need all that power for?
不知道
I don't know,
我想这是第一次有选手从房间里出来
I think we're the first ever contestants to get outside.
我有两个朋友跟我一起
I had two friends traveling with me,
他们一定也被传送过来了
they must've got caught in the same transmat,
他们会在哪儿
where would they be?
我不知道 被分配到哪儿都有可能
I don't know, they could have been allocated anywhere,
这儿有100种不同的游戏
there's 100 different games.
比如
Like what?
有十层都是《老大哥》
Well, there's ten floors of Big Brother,
每扇门后面都是一间老大哥之家
there's a different house behind each of those doors,
还有其他各种娱乐节目 不停歇播出
and beyond that there's all sorts of shows, it's non-stop.
有用真枪的《吹牛游戏》
There's, em...Call My Bluff with real guns,
要在30秒内解除炸弹的《倒计时》
Countdown where you've got 30 seconds to stop the bomb going off.
《大地力量》更凶残 选手会被变成肥料
Ground Force, which is a nasty one, you get turned into compost.
还有《一扫而净》不言自明
Erm...Wipeout, speaks for itself,
还有《满眼金星》不是比喻
oh, and Stars In Their Eyes, literally,
《满眼金星》如果不唱 他们就弄瞎你
stars in their eyes - if you don't sing, you get blinded.
你们还看这些节目
And you watch this stuff?
每个人都看 你怎么没看
Everyone does. How come you don't?
没交过电视费
I never paid for my licence.
天呐 你会被处决的
Oh, my God, you get executed for that!
让他们试试
Let'em try.
你说的话都不合常理
You keep saying things that don't make sense.
你到底是什么人 博士
Who are you, though, Doctor, really?
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
对我来说很重要 我把命都交到了你手里
Well, it does to me. I've just put my life in your hands.
我不过是路过的旅客
I'm a traveller wandering past.
信不信由你 我不过想平静过一生
Believe it or not, all I'm after is a quiet life.
如果我们离开这里
So... if we get out of here,
你会去干什么 继续游荡
what are you gonna do, just... wander off again?
越快越好
Fast as I can.
要知道 我可以跟你一起去
Cos, em... I could come with ya.
也许可以
Maybe you could.
我不会妨碍到你
I wouldn't get in the way.
那倒无所谓
I wouldn't mind if you did.
是个好主意 王字边的琳达
Not a bad idea, Lynda with a Y.
但首先 我们要集中精力出去
But first of all we've gotta concentrate on the getting out,
成功的前提是 知己知彼
and to do that, you've got to know your enemy.
现在谁做主
Who's controlling it?
谁控制着这个卫星
Who's in charge of the satellite now?
等一下
Hold on...
恶狼集团
你要找的就是他们
Your lords and masters.
好吧 你赢了 需要主控来处理他们
OK, you win, the Controller's got to handle this.
所有传输活动都会记录归档
Archive makes a record of all transmat activities.
我去看看他怎么上来的 六号档案馆
Find out how he got on board. Archive Six.
主控
Controller...
我们这里有个问题
we have a problem.
继续工作
Continue working.
我们有安全隐患
We have a security problem.
继续工作
Continue working.
对不起 但是我不能 有选手离开了游戏
I'm sorry, but I can't. We have contestants outside the games,
但是警报没有响
but the alarms haven't gone off.
没有安全隐患 游戏继续
No security, the games continue.
我们不能让他们到处溜达
We can't just let them wander.
他们无关紧要
They are no-one.
他们不值一提
对不起 我只是
I'm sorry, I was just, erm...
六号档案馆无法开启
Archive Six is out of bounds.
但是我需要检查传输记录
But I need to check the transmat log.
六号档案馆无法开启
Archive Six is out of bounds.
任何人不得进入六号档案馆
No-one may enter Archive Six.
回去工作
Return to work.
通知全体员工 太阳耀斑将出现在Δ.7
Inform all staff, solar flares in delta point seven.
19 20
19, 20...
系统兼容
Compatible systems...
只用调整波信号
Just align the wave signature...
好样的 我给自己弄了把枪
That-a-boy! Got myself a gun!
女士们 我很开心
Well, ladies, the pleasure was all mine,
到最后这才是最重要的
which is the only thing that matters in the end.
两颗心 是他
Two hearts, that's him.
哪一层
Which floor?
天呐
Blimey!
我从未亲眼见过 没有在轨道上见过
I've never seen it for real before, not from orbit.
地球
Planet Earth!
发生了什么
What's happened to it?
从我出生就是这样了 看见那个了吗
It's always been like that,ever since I was born. See that there?
那是大西洋巨型烟尘暴
That's the Great Atlantic Smog Storm.
20年过去了仍未停歇
That's been going for 20 years.
有新闻通知我们 什么时候可以外出呼吸
We get newsflashes, telling us when it's safe to breathe outside.
所以全人类就坐着
So the population just sits there.
一半人太胖 一半人太瘦
Half the world's too fat, half's too thin,
你们就坐着看电视
and you lot just watch telly.
一万个频道 都由这里播出
10,000 channels, all beaming down from here.
人类啊 无脑的绵羊 维生只依赖…
The human race! Brainless sheep, being fed on a diet of...
对了 还有没有那个
Mind you, have they still got that programme
三个人和一只熊住在一起的节目
where three people live with a bear?
《熊与我》我超爱那个节目
Oh, Bear With Me, I love that one!
我也是 明星版里 熊去泡澡…
And me. The celebrity edition where the bear got in the bath...
但是一切都错了 历史又一次出错了
But it's all gone wrong, I mean, history's gone wrong, again!
现在这里应该是伟大富饶的人类第四帝国
This should be the Fourth Great and Bountiful Human Empire.
我不明白 上次我来的时候已经纠正了错误
I don't understand. Last time I was here I put it right.
但就是从那时候起一切都变了
No, but that's when it first went wrong,
100年前 如你所说
100 years ago, like you said.
所有的新闻频道 一夜间全部消失
All the news channels, they just shut down overnight.
但那是我干的
But that was me. I did that.
没有别的东西播出
There was nothing left in their place,
没有信息 整个星球停止了
no information. The whole planet froze.
政府和经济都崩溃了
The government, the economy, they collapsed.
那就是开头
That was the start of it,
100年的地狱
100 years of hell.
天
Oh, my...
这是我一手造成的
I made this world.
现在剩下洛斯和罗德里克一对一
That leaves Rose and Rodrick, you're going head-to-head.
让我们继续进行《智者为王》
Let's play...The Weakest Link!
战术性投票到此为止
That's the end of tactical voting.
你得靠自己了
You're on your own now.
帅哥 很高兴见到你啊
Hey, handsome, good to see you.
知道洛斯在哪儿吗 -你不能追踪到她吗
Any sign of Rose? - Can't you track her down?
她一定还在游戏里 所有房间都被屏蔽了
She must be still inside the games, all the rooms are shielded.
如果我可以连上电脑
If I can get inside this computer.
她肯定在这里某个地方
She's got to be here somewhere.
快点 这些游戏的结局可不太好看
You'd better hurry up, these games don't have a happy ending.
你以为我不知道吗
You think I don't know that? !
给 连上电脑 已经编好搜寻程序了
There you go. Patch that in, it's programmed to find her.
谢了
Thanks.
好啊 -你好
Hey, there. - Hello!
杰克·哈克尼斯上校 -琳达·莫斯
Captain Jack Harkness. - Lynda Moss.
很高兴认识你 琳达·莫斯
Nice to meet you, Lynda Moss.
要调情出去调
Do you mind flirting outside?
我只是问好而已
I was just saying hello!
对你来说那也是调情
For you, that's flirting.
我不介意 -感激不尽
I'm not complaining. - Muchas gracias.
不兼容 这该死的系统完全没道理
Not compatible! This stupid system doesn't make sense!
这里应该是播放基地
This place should be a basic broadcaster,
但是这个系统过于复杂了
but the systems are twice as complicated.
不止是电视 这里还传送别的什么东西
It's more than TV, this station's transmitting something else.
比如什么
Like what?
不知道 但是我摆脱不掉这个恶狼
I don't know. This whole Bad Wolf thing's tied up with me.
有人在一直操纵我
Someone's manipulating my entire life,
这是某种陷阱 而洛斯却陷在了里面
it's some sort of trap, and Rose is stuck inside it.
洛斯 地理知识 中央大峡谷是
Rose, in geography, the Grand Central Ravine
以哪个古英国城市命名
is named after which ancient British city?
是约克吗
Is it York?
错 正确答案是谢菲尔德
No, the correct answer is Sheffield.
找到了 407层
Found her! Floor 407.
天呐 她跟安卓机器人在一起 快把她救出来
Oh, my God, she's with the Anne-droid, get her out of there!
罗德里克
Rodrick,
文学知识《好运》作者姓什么
in literature, the author of Lucky was Jackie who?
斯图尔特
Stewart.
错 正确答案是柯林斯
No, the correct answer is Collins.
洛斯 艾索普星系最古老的居民是什么之脸
Rose, the oldest inhabitant of the Isop Galaxy is the face of what?
伯欧 伯欧之脸
Boe! The Face of Boe!
回答正确
That is the correct answer.
快点 快点
Come on! Come on!
罗德里克 历史知识 红丝绒的总统是谁
Rodrick, in history who was the president of the Red Velvets?
霍史宾·福林
Hoshbin Frane.
回答正确
That is correct.
洛斯 菜肴中
Rose, in food,
盖福别克这道菜起源于哪个星球
the dish gaffabeque originated on which planet?
是不是
Em...Is it...?
火星
Mars?
错 正确答案是路西法星
No, the correct answer is Lucifer.
罗德里克 以杰特大帝从鼻子到指尖的距离
Rodrick, which measurement of length is said to have been defined
定义的长度单位是什么
by the Emperor Jate as the distance from his nose to his fingertip?
是哥福吗
Would that be a goffle?
错 正确答案是帕布
No, the correct answer is a paab.
洛斯 时尚知识
Rose, in fashion,
斯黛拉·波克·本特因什么而出名
Stella Pok Baint is famous for what?
鞋
Shoes.
错 正确答案是帽子
No. The correct answer is hats.
罗德里克
Rodrick...
六号游戏室是哪个
Game Room Six, which one is it?
这边
Over here!
珊·海瑟汀
San Hazeldine.
错 正确答案是陈三
No, the correct answer is San Chen.
让我把门炸开
Let me blast it open.
炸不开的 需要生物密码
You can't, it's a vital combination.
洛斯 历史上
Rose, in history,
哪个冰岛城市举行了第20届大逃杀
which Icelandic city hosted Murder Spree 20?
雷克雅未克
Reykjavik?
错 正确答案是宝拉文图拉
No, the correct answer is Pola Ventura.
天呐 我赢了 你输了
Oh, my God! I've done it! You've lost!
快点 快点 快点
Come on, come on, come on!
罗德里克
Rodrick...
但是我本不该在这里
I'm not mean to be here.
你是最强一环
You ARE the strongest link.
我要去找博士 他肯定在这里某个地方
I need to find the Doctor, he's gotta be here somewhere!
他不会抛弃我
He wouldn't just leave me!
十分感谢
Thank you so much.
这个游戏是违法的 我警告你立刻停止
This game is illegal, I'm telling you to stop!
洛斯 停止这个游戏
Rose! Stop this game!
我命令你们停止这个游戏
I order you to stop this game!
你是最弱一环
You are the weakest link...
小心安卓机器人 它有武器
Look out for the Anne-droid, it's armed!
你把她怎么了
What the hell did you do to her?
我要叫保安了 你们没有权利出现在这里
I'm calling security, you have no permission to be here.
关闭安卓机器人
Deactivate the Anne-droid.
你杀了她 而你在乎的只是钱
You killed her and all you're worried about money?
后退 先生 后退
Back off, Mister! Back off!
主控 我需要跳过你的指令
Control, I'm overriding your commands,
我需要保安 现在就要
I need security, and I need it here right now!
就是那群人
It's that lot...
别碰他
Leave him alone!
先生 放下你的枪 不然我要开枪了
Sir, put down the gun or I'll have to shoot.
你们杀了她 你们的变态游戏节目害死了她
You killed her! Your stupid freaking game show killed her!
先生 我以游戏基站企业联合会
Sir, I'm arresting you under Private Legislation 16
私人法令第16条的名义逮捕你
of the Game Station Syndicate...
先生 能否告诉我们这个仪器的用途
Can you tell us the purpose of this device, sir?
能否告诉我们你们是如何来到这里的
Can you tell us how you got on board?
别烦他了
Just leave him alone.
我在问他
I'm asking him.
先生 能否告诉我们你是谁
Sir? Can you tell us who you are?
你们将被押送至月球监狱
You will be taken from this place to the lunar penal colony,
即刻开始服刑
to be held without trial.
不得上诉
You may not appeal against this sentence.
明白了吗
Is that understood?
动手
Let's do it.
天呐 我们有麻烦了
Oh, my God, now we're in trouble.
500层
Floor 500.
所有人员撤离
Clear the floor!
他就要上来了 带着枪
He's on his way up here... With a gun!
紧急事态 请封锁电梯
This is an emergency, you've got to close down the lift.
所有员工请注意 太阳耀斑即将开始
All staff are reminded that solar flares commence...
别管太阳耀斑了 他会杀了你的
Never mind solar flares, he's gonna kill you!
好了 离开桌子 谁都不许耍花招
OK, move away from the desk. Nobody try anything clever.
所有人让开 站到两边不要动
Everybody clear, stand to the side and stay there.
谁控制着这里
Who's in charge of this place?
19 20
19, 20...
这个卫星不仅仅是游戏基站那么简单
This satellite's more than a game station.
79 80
79, 80...
谁杀了洛斯·泰勒
Who killed Rose Tyler?
所有员工请注意
All staff are reminded...
回答我
I want an answer!
坐标Δ.1
in delta point one.
她无法回应
She can't reply.
别开枪
Don't shoot!
别傻了 我怎么会开枪
Oh, don't be so thick, like I was ever gonna shoot.
上校 又有保安上来了
Captain, we've got more guards on the way up,
守住出口 -遵命
Secure the exits. - Yes, sir!
你 你刚说什么
You! What were you saying?
但是我拿着你的枪
But...I've got your gun.
那冲我开枪啊 为什么她不能回答我
OK, so shoot me.Why can't she answer?
她…我能把枪放下吗
She's, erm... Can I put this down?
想放就放 动作快点 -谢了
If you want, just hurry up. - Thanks.
抱歉
Sorry, erm...
主控是播送程序的一部分
The Controller is linked into the transmissions,
所有的输出信号都要经过她的大脑
the entire output goes through her brain.
你不是这里的员工 她无法识别你的存在
You're not a member of staff, so she doesn't recognise your existence.
她叫什么
What's her name?
我不知道 她五岁时就被安装在这里了
I don't know. She was installed when she was five years old,
她只有那短短五年的人生
that's the only life she's ever known.
梯门封锁 我们有十分钟时间
Doors sealed, we're safe for about ten minutes.
盯着他们
Keep an eye on 'em.
你说游戏基站有什么事在发生
That stuff you said about something going on with the Game Station,
我想你是对的
I think you're right.
我记录了所有未经授权的传输和加密信号
I've kept a log, unauthorised transmats, encrypted signals.
已经持续了很多年了
It's been going on for years.
让我看
Show me.
你不能进去 六号档案馆是禁地
You're not allowed in there, Archive Six is out of bounds.
你觉得我是那种守规矩的人吗
Do I look like an out-of-bounds sort of guy?
搞什么
What the hell... ?
太阳耀斑活动
Solar flare activity in delta...
如果我们不是你的人质 那就开门
If you're not holding us hostage, open the door,
放我们走 员工都吓死了
let us out, the staff are terrified!
处死了数百游戏选手的员工居然还有情感
That's the same staff who execute hundreds of contestants?
这不能怪我们 我们只是尽职尽责
That's not our fault, we're just doing our jobs.
就凭你这句话 你已经失去了跟我说话的资格
With that sentence you just lost the right to even talk to me,
退后
now back off!
太阳耀斑开始了
That's just the solar flares.
太阳耀斑会干扰播送信号
They interfere with the broadcast signal,
所以这里会自动断电
so this place automatically powers down.
地球上会重播节目
Planet Earth gets a few repeats.
这都很正常
It's all quite normal.
博士
Doctor...
Doctor?
无论如何 你都先等着
Whatever it is, you can wait.
我觉得她想找你
I think she wants you.
博士 博士 博士在哪里
Doctor... Doctor...Where's the Doctor?
我在这儿
I'm here.
我看不见 失明 一片漆黑 一生漆黑
I can't see, blind...So blind, all my life blind.
我能看见的只有数字 但是我看见了你
All I can see is numbers, but I saw you.
你想要什么
What do you want?
太阳耀斑可以掩护我 他们现在听不见我
Solar flares hiding me, they can't hear me.
我的主人一直在监听 但是他们现在听不见
My masters listen, but they can't hear me now, the sun,
太阳 太阳如此明亮
the sun is so bright.
你的主人是谁
Who are your masters?
他们改写我的大脑 我无法说出他们的名字
They wired my head, the name is forbidden.
他们控制了我的大脑 我的主人
They control my thoughts, my masters,
我的主人 我得小心
my masters, I had to be careful.
他们监控着播送信号 但是他们不看节目
They monitor transmission. But they don't watch the programmes.
我可以把你藏在游戏里 知道你会找到我的
I could hide you inside the games, knew that you woulld find me.
我的朋友死在了你的游戏里
My friend died inside your games.
没关系
It doesn't matter.
你怎么敢跟我说那没关系
Don't you dare tell me that!
他们一直在躲藏
They've been hiding,
我的主人 躲在暗处
my masters, hiding in the dark space,
监视 控制着地球
watching and shaping the Earth,
很多很多年
so... so... so many years.
一直在那里 引导着人类
Always been there, guiding humanity,
成百上千年
hundreds and hundreds of years.
他们是谁
Who are they?
他们等待 他们谋划 他们增殖
They wait and plan and grow in numbers,
现在他们变得强大 如此强大 我的主人
they're strong now, so strong, my masters.
他们是谁
Who are they?
但是提起你
But speak of you.
我的主人 他们惧怕博士
My masters, they fear the Doctor.
告诉我 他们是谁
Tell me! Who are they?
下一次太阳耀斑是什么时候
When's the next solar flare?
两年后
Two years' time.
那有个屁用
Fat lot of good that is!
我找到了塔迪斯
Found the Tardis.
我们现在不能走
We're not leaving now.
好 但是塔迪斯算出来了
No, but the Tardis worked it out.
你肯定喜欢这个
You'll wanna watch this.
琳达 能请你站到那边去吗
Lynda, could you stand over there for me, please?
我只想回家
I just wanna go home.
一会儿就好
It'll only take a second,
你能站到那个位置上吗 快一点
could you stand in that spot? Quick as you can!
所有人注意
Everybody watching?
三 二 一
OK, three, two, one.
你杀了她
But you killed her!
你觉得是这样吗
Oh, do you think?
那是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
那只是物质粒子传输射线
It's a transmat beam,
不是解体射线 是次级传输系统
not a disintegrator, a secondary transmat system.
游戏里没有人死
People don't get killed in the games,
他们不过是被传输到了别的地方
they get transported across Space.
博士 洛斯还活着
Doctor, Rose is still alive!
不 这不可能是真的
No, it can't be.
我亲眼看见你死了的
I saw you die!
她还在某个地方
She's out there somewhere!
博士 坐标5.6.1
Doctor! Coordinates 5.6.1.434
别 太阳耀斑已经结束 他们会听见你的
Don't, the solar flare's gone now, they'll hear you!
不 我的主人 不 我要反抗你
No, my masters, no, I defy you!
∑7
Sigma 7...
他们掳走了她
They took her.
我的主人
Oh, my masters...
你们可以杀了我
you can kill me...
因为我为你们带来了毁灭
for I have brought your destruction.
给 用这个 可能含有最后的坐标
Look, use that. It might contain the final numbers,
我记录了所有计划外的传输
I kept a log of all the unscheduled transmissions.
好样的 谢谢
Nice... Thanks.
顺便自我介绍一下 杰克·哈克尼斯上校
Captain Jack Harkness, by the way.
大卫奇·帕威尔
I'm Davitch Pavale.
很高兴认识你 大卫奇·帕威尔
Nice to meet you, Davitch Pavale.
注意下场合
There's a time and a place.
你是说这整个设施都只是掩饰吗
Are you saying that this whole set-up's been a disguise all along?
很早就开始了 一百年前加戈菲斯就是他们安置的
Going way back, installing the Jagrafess 100 years ago.
有人放长线钓大鱼
Someone's been playing a long game,
在幕后控制了人类几代人
controlling the human race from behind the scenes for generations.
按一下
Click on this.
传输射线的终点就是那里
The transmat delivers to that point,
就在太阳系的边缘
right on the edge of the solar system.
但是那里什么也没有
But there's nothing there.
看上去什么也没有 是因为这个卫星的作用
It looks like nothing because that's what this satellite does.
传输信号之下还有另一个信号
Underneath the transmission there's another signal.
在做什么
Doing what?
隐藏那里的东西
Hiding whatever's out there.
使其不会被声纳 雷达 扫描发现
Hiding it from sonar, radar, scanner.
有什么东西就在地球身边
There's something's sitting right on top of Planet Earth,
但却又完全隐形
but it's completely invisible.
如果我关闭那个信号
If I cancel the signal...
不可能
That's impossible.
我认识那些战舰 他们被摧毁了
I know those ships. They were destroyed.
显然他们幸存了下来
Obviously, they survived.
你们说谁 他们是谁
Who did? Who are they?
200艘战舰
200 ships.
每艘战舰上有超过2000个
More than 2, 000 on board each one.
一共是将近50万个
That's just about half a million of them.
50万个什么
Half a million what?
戴立克
Daleks.
警报 警报 我们被发现了
Alert! Alert! We are detected!
博士来了 他已将我们定位
It is the Doctor! He has located us!
开启通讯频道
Open communications channel!
那个女性 起立 起立
The female will stand! Stand!
我要和博士对话
I will talk to the Doctor.
是吗 挺好 你好
Oh, will you? That's nice, hello!
戴立克计划已接近尾声
The Dalek stratagem nears completion.
舰队即将整备完成 你不得干涉
The fleet is almost ready. You will not intervene.
是吗 那是为什么
Oh, really? Why's that, then?
我们抓到了你的同伴
We have your associate.
你不服从她就会被消灭
You will obey or she will be exterminated.
不
No.
请解释
Explain yourself.
我说了 不
I said "No".
你的否定是什么意思
What is the meaning of this negative?
不就是不
It means no.
但她将被毁灭
But she will be destroyed!
不
No...
因为 接下来我要做的是
Cos this is what I'M gonna do.
我会拯救她
I'm gonna rescue her,
我会从戴立克舰队中救回洛斯·泰勒
I'm gonna save Rose Tyler from the middle of the Dalek fleet,
然后我要拯救地球 最后作为收尾
and then I'm gonna save the Earth, and then just to finish off,
我要清除宇宙中每一只恶臭的戴立克
I'm gonna wipe every last stinking Dalek out of the sky!
但是你没有武器 没有防御 没有计划
But you have no weapons, no defences, no plan!
没错
Yeah...
是不是吓死你们了
and doesn't that scare you to death?
洛斯 -我在 博士
Rose? - Yes, Doctor?
我来找你了
I'm coming to get you.
博士开始敌对行动
The Doctor is initiating hostile action!
必须进行下一步计划
The statagem must advance!
开始侵略地球
Begin the invasion of Earth!
博士将被消灭
The Doctor will be exterminated!
消灭 消灭
Exterminate! Exterminate!
消灭
Exterminate!
消灭 消灭
Exterminate! Exterminate!
发射导弹 消灭
Launch missiles, exterminate.
下集预告
导弹来袭
We've got incoming!
女士们 先生们 战争开始
This is it, ladies and gentlemen, we are at war.
有一只军队即将入侵基站
There's an army about to invade this station.
防御系统下线
Defences have gone off-line.
我已经身亡 或是无法逃脱 即将身亡
I'm dead or about to die any second with no chance of escape.
你们怎么从时间大战中存活了下来
How did you survive the Time War?
是我就救了他们
They survived through me!